[English subtitles are available]
[Song Of The Moon]
[Episode 13]
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Brother, sister-in-law,
you are leaving tomorrow.
Before you leave,
we shall give you a toast.
Later,
you'll go to the Immortal Palace to observe the ceremony.
Then we will meet again.
Well...
It will be in the Immortal Palace.
But now, we can feel at ease here.
Let's just
have fun tonight.
Cheers.
-Cheers! -Cheers!
[Sword Washing Pavilion]
Lu Li.
What are you doing?
I'm looking at the moon on the willow branch.
You should look at the willow branch [referring to Liu Shao] in front of you.
Liu Shao.
It's said there is a way
that can help me stay with you forever.
Then no one can separate us apart.
Do you think I should give it a try?
Try it.
Of course you should.
Maybe we can give it a try.
But will it really
be as simple as what my master described?
The seal of the Four Seasons Tablet is getting weaker.
I hope this disciple of Marquis Wuyang
can really help the Immortal Palace get the Four Seasons Tablet restored.
Aren't we going to the Immortal Palace?
Why did you get a fish?
Take a guess.
Guess whether I'll guess or not.
Do you know?
It's said that
mortals will be reborn
as long as they enter the Immortal Palace,
gaining unimaginably wonderful life.
Come on.
Be careful.
Get ready.
Now is the real start.
Look over there.
[Immortal Palace]
Immortal Master?
I've seen you before.
Nice to meet you, Immortal Master.
Nice to meet you, Immortal Master Wanwu.
That day,
Marquis Wuyang asked me to look over the arrival of Immortal,
I saw you two
through the Mansion's Xuantian Mirror.
So this time,
was it you who gave me the chance?
It was the Bone-Corroding Harp
that gave you the chance.
You are the new heir chosen by Marquis Wuyang?
You're quite handsome.
I feel flattered.
I'm far from reaching Marquis Wuyang's cultivation.
Immortal Master.
It's you?
What?
You know them?
Fine then,
I'll leave these two
to you.
Okay.
Take care, Immortal Master.
Greetings, General. Xie.
I have business to do.
You two just
go to Palace Wuji
and settle down in the residence
for low-rank disciples.
Palace Wuji?
General. Xie!
Where is Palace Wuji?
Where can we find it without you telling us?
Don't worry. Since we're here, let's take it easy.
Let's go.
Let me show you around
to get familiar with the environment.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
Let's go over there.
Actually, I've been here when young.
You've been to the Immortal Palace before?
Look.
This is the magic taught in the Immortal Palace?
Look at their posture.
Just like so, right?
Do I look like them?
Look.
There are waterfalls in the sky?
But you should have seen it before.
I just took a look from afar.
Lu Li.
I wish this could last forever.
Are you really going to stay here forever?
I just want
to be with you forever.
I'm now under the Four Seasons Tablet.
As long as I pull out the Moon Sword,
I can be with Liu Shao forever.
But Liu Shao was ordered to repair the Tablet.
Should I tell this to her?
Lu Li.
Why are you spacing out?
I went to wash some fruits just now.
Have a taste to see whether it's sweet.
Is it sweet?
You too.
I wonder what's the need of cultivating
for these immortals.
Our life now
should be what immortals's life is like.
They asked me to cultivate myself here.
But...
I've been here for so many days.
They didn't give me any classes.
Classes?
They only want your Bone-Corroding Harp.
As long as you help get the Four Seasons Tablet restored,
they definitely will accept you.
But if I fail to get it restored,
will they drive me back?
What are you thinking?
You know what?
They've prepared a lot
to repair the Four Seasons Tablet.
They just want to make use
of the Bone-Corroding Harp's healing effect.
If
you fail to get it repaired,
and ruin their plan,
then...
you will directly
be thrown under the waterfall for feeding the fish.
You've made the Immortal Palace described
more terrifying than Ao Hen.
It doesn't matter.
Maybe I can get the Four Seasons Tablet restored.
By then,
I can beg them
to let you stay here together with me.
In that case,
I would appreciate it a lot, Miss Liu.
You're welcome.
But you...
you still have to take charge of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
What if they don't allow me to go back?
Boring.
Let me show you this.
What is this?
Here you go.
This is the magic doll?
Yes.
On the day when you drew the sword,
Bai Feng used this to deceive you.
Unfortunately, I don't have enough power.
I can only conjure myself.
But my master.
can not only conjure me,
but also...
Don't be angry anymore.
From now on, I'll never
be cheated by these things again.
I will believe you in the future.
I only
trust you,
not what I see with my eyes,
or what I hear with my ears.
I'll only believe you.
What?
Are you here to laugh at me?
I just want to laugh at the Immortal Palace.
Are you interested?
No.
I just want to
burn down the Immortal Palace
and use all of their blood inside
to worship my son, Ao Yin.
Let's do it together.
They're going to repair the Four Seasons Tablet tomorrow.
We can watch the ceremony.
Tomorrow?
But there will be protection spells cast
outside the Immortal Palace.
Can you really get in?
Where is Liu Shao?
Liu Shao.
You asked me out
to talk about repairing the Four Seasons Tablet?
No, no.
I've treated myself with the Bone-Corroding Harp.
I can feel its power.
It won't go wrong.
Then you are...
It's about Lu Li.
He had the Soul-Devouring Spell cast upon him.
Although
it's temporarily quelled,
But this is not a long-term solution.
So I want to say,
if I can get the Four Seasons Tablet restored,
can the Immortal Palace help
remove the Soul-Devouring Spell from him?
I can give up the chance to cultivate in the Immortal Palace.
I only wish...
for Lu Li's safety and well-being.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm very sure.
We'll talk about it after you restore the Four Seasons Tablet.
Have you really decided?
Of course.
But mortals
won't live long.
I don't want
to cultivate alone for thousands of years.
I always wanted to go to the Immortal Palace
and marry an immortal.
But now,
I have you.
As long as I'm with you for this life,
I don't think it's a loss.
No.
It will be my fortune.
A great fortune.
Okay.
I'll ask Lord to be the matchmaker after we go back,
and go propose marriage to you.
Maybe there will be a lucky day for us
to get married this year.
By the way,
when we get married,
we should invite Wang Jian and Xue.
And He Na.
You're right.
We can't forget him.
Although
I really don't like that fake fish demon.
By then,
we can build a house next to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Yes.
We need to raise a rabbit.
Okay.
And sheep.
My Lord.
Brother.
This way, please.
Today is the day
for the Immortal Palace and the Mortal World
to celebrate the grand event.
A song to mend the heaven
so that the friendship between immortals and mortals will be eternal.
Rise!
What a big scene!
So,
this is how the Immortal Palace
protect the human world.
Today,
I will also become one to protect the mortal world.
Liu Shao.
Play the Bone-Corroding Harp
to restore the Four Seasons Tablet.
Concentrate.
Calm down.
Bone-Corroding Harp.
Out.
Look over there.
The cracks are decreasing.
Yes.
It's getting restored.
Senior Liu is amazing.
Yes.
As expected of Senior Liu Shao.
My sister-in-law is amazing.
Keep your voice down.
What's the need of hiding it?
My sister-in-law is indeed amazing.
Even if my sister-in-law has become a disciple in the Immortal Palace,
she's still my sister-in-law.
Enough.
The Bone-Corroding Harp
seems to be calling someone.
Liu Shao.
Thank you for bringing the Bone-Corroding Harp to the Four Seasons Tablet.
Now, it's my turn.
This harp...
It's stealing my vitality.
No.
Qiuxian.
Lingqi.
Steady the formation.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Stop!
Immortal Master.
Look at the Four Seasons Tablet.
We can't suppress it.
What should we do?
I can't control the Bone-Corroding Harp.
What's wrong with Liu Shao?
Is she going to destroy the Four Seasons Tablet?
Liu Shao, what are you doing?
Do your best.
Don't let that devil come out.
Change the formation!
It seems that the Bone-Corroding Harp
is out of Liu Shao's control.
Liu Shao!
No!
A demon's attacking the Zijin Shield.
It's trying to break the protection spells.
Oh, no.
Sister-in-law is still up there.
Lay out the formation!
Disciples of Marquis Wuyang, listen up.
Protect the Four Seasons Tablet!
Yes.
Xie Lingqi.
Pay with your life for my son's death.
You overestimated yourself.
Let me see who else can stop me.
My Lord.
Marquis Wuyang.
Bone-Corroding Harp! No!
Soul-Devouring Spell?
Why would it break out at this moment?
Liu Shao, no.
I can't hold on anymore.
Liu Shao.
Is this what's called
having no choice...
Lu Li.
Did you see it clearly?
Your beloved one,
your friends,
and your fellows
are dying.
When the Soul-Devouring Spell is fully triggered,
you will die soon.
Are you satisfied?
Pick up the Moon Sword,
break the Four Seasons Tablet
and revive God of the Moonlight.
As long as you have the power of God,
all spirits in the Three Realms
will follow your order.
Everything
will be under your control.
Lu Li.
If you want to protect Liu Shao,
go and break the Four Seasons Tablet.
To break the Four Seasons Tablet
can get them saved.
Lu Li!
Protect the Four Seasons Tablet!
Once it's destroyed,
and the devil comes out,
the Three Realms will be in hell.
All spirits will suffer.
All spirits will suffer...
Everything will be in hell.
Break the Four Seasons Tablet
to get the power of God
so that you can truly protect them.
Lu Li.
What are you waiting for?
Why are you hesitating?
Look at your dead fellows.
Your current power can't save anyone.
Get up!
Help them protect the Four Seasons Tablet!
Break the Four Seasons Tablet.
I won't break the Four Seasons Tablet.
To revive God of the Moonlight,
will make the Three Realms suffer.
I won't let that happen.
I won't!
Lu Li.
Don't disappoint me.
The future
is on you.
Ridiculous.
Let me see what you can do now.
Damn.
I've protected the world for my whole life.
Even if I have to sacrifice,
I won't allow you to tread on it.
My Lord!
No.
I can't be restrained by the Bone-Corroding Harp anymore.
I'm the one who plays the Harp.
I am.
Liu Shao!
Lu Li!
Lu Li.
I wanted to heal my injury with Liu Shao's divine spirit.
But
you've come here to die first.
Lu Li!
You humble mortals...
You only deserve to be my son's burial objects.
In the end,
I still can't
protect the ones I want to protect?
Lu Li.
Why should mortals die just because they're mortals?
Mortals also have things they want to defend,
and people they want to protect.
Lu Li.
The Moon Sword!
How can the Moon Sword regard a mortal as its master?
Do you remember what I said when we met?
Even if I'm not the most powerful one,
I dare to fight against everything,
no matter how strong or weak the opponent is.
No!
To be a God
by sacrificing my friends and my beloved one.
I won't do that.
I just want to be a mortal
to fight alongside them.
Impossible.
Xue.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
Slow down.
Brother.
Brother!
Lu Li!
Brother.
Brother!
Lu Li.
No.
Liu Shao.
I've promised you to be with you forever.
I...
I may be not able to make it.
No.
You've promised me.
Don't lie to me.
I said
I would take care of you forever.
Unfortunately,
I still can't
protect you anymore.
I don't want you to protect me.
I only want you to be fine.
I just want you to be fine.
Your safety is more important than anything.
Promise me. Please.
-You must be fine. -Stop crying.
Don't cry.
Please.
We...
See you in the next life.
No.
We promised to be good.
We agreed to be together forever.
Lu Li, I beg you.
Don't leave me.
Please.
In this life,
I feel lucky to meet you.
Sorry for failing to be with you forever.
But I never regret meeting you.
♫This is a spring song♫
♫The peach blossoms fly with the swallow♫
♫Whose lights are light and shine people's way home?♫
♫The clouds roll the sunset♫
♫The moon kisses the eyebrows♫
♫I am waiting for you to say♫
♫Tonight in this life♫
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
♫I miss you so much♫
♫I still remember the youth♫
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
Actually I've long discovered that my life
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
is in the hands of others.
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
In this world
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
I've gone through,
I was just like a shadow,
without leaving anything behind.
♫Send you to the Western State♫
But I met you.
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
Lu Li.
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
Your words may be a little bit harsh.
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
But
when everyone suspected me,
only you would trust me and help me.
30,000 taels?
Awesome!
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
Then I...
♫I miss you so much♫
I'll ask Lord to be the matchmaker after we go back.
Maybe there will be a lucky day for us
to get married this year.
♫I still remember the youth♫
Liu Shao!
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
-Lu Li! -Liu Shao!
Lu Li!
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
Then set a time limit.
Make it last...
♫Send you to the Western State♫
to the moment when I can't protect my beloved one,
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
no more needed by anyone,
and come to the end of my life.
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
Lu Li.
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
I was born with only half a heart.
Now,
I've found the other half.
It's you.
Liar!
Let's catch the moon!
Don't miss it.
Miss.
I said it's true, but you don't believe me.
I've been here before.
The immortal brought me here.
Miss.
Miss, slow down.
So cute.
When I find my immortal,
I will ask him to take me to see
mountains, the sun, the moon, and stars everywhere.
To catch the moon!
Don't miss it.
Let's catch the moon.
I've once thought about
whether the promise
was just a dream or not.
Because I can't remember his face.
If you leave your fate in my hands,
I can play with you for three days.
We can go to
the most interesting
and funnest places all over the world.
But if I don't believe in myself,
then the three days
can only be a dream.
Only by believing it
can the promise
be real.
Immortal?